<resources>
    <string name="AppName">SaveNote</string>
    <string name="DeleteSelected">Delete Selected?</string>
    <string name="SearchNotes">Search Notes</string>
    <string name="BackButton">Back Button</string>
    <string name="DeleteNote">Delete Note</string>
    <string name="Title">Title</string>
    <string name="Note">Note</string>
    <string name="DeleteConfirm">Delete</string>
    <string name="DeleteCancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="Check">Check entry</string>
    <string name="AddEntry">Add Entry</string>
    <string name="ShareList">Share list</string>
    <string name="ReArrange">Re-arrange</string>
    <string name="ShowCompleted">Show completed</string>
    <string name="HideCompleted">Hide completed</string>
    <string name="UncheckEntries">Uncheck All</string>
    <string name="DeleteChecked">Delete Checked</string>
    <string name="Backup">Backup</string>
    <string name="Restore">Restore</string>
    <string name="Help">Help</string>
    <string name="Menu">Menu</string>
    <string name="ListOnly">List</string>
    <string name="BackUp">Back-up</string>
    <string name="RateApp">Rate app</string>
    <string name="Newest">Newest</string>
    <string name="Oldest">Oldest</string>
    <string name="Sort">Sort-by:</string>
    <string name="LastEdit">Last edited</string>
    <string name="ShowMore">Show more</string>
    <string name="ShowLess">Show less</string>
    <string name="Instructions">Instructions</string>
    <string name="ConfirmDelete">All %s notes will be permanently deleted.</string>
    <string name="BackupStep1">Backing Up Your Notes:</string>
    <string name="BackupStep2">Click the backup button to start the backup process. This will prompt you to select a location to save the backup file. We recommend choosing a location that you are familiar with, such as your downloads folder. However, it\'s important to store the backup file in a secure location, such as cloud storage, to prevent data loss.</string>
    <string name="BackupStep3">Once you have selected the location, save the backup file. If you plan on using the backup file later, make sure to remember where you saved it.</string>
    <string name="BackupStep4">If you do not have a secure location to store the backup file, it\'s recommended to delete the file once you are done with the restore process.</string>
    <string name="RestoreNoteHeader">Restoring Your Notes:</string>
    <string name="NoMatches">No matches found</string>
    <string name="TapToConfirm">Tap to confirm</string>
    <string name="RestoreStep1">Click on the restore button when you are ready to restore your notes. This will prompt you to select the backup file that you previously saved.</string>
    <string name="RestoreStep2">Browse to the location where you saved the backup file and select it. If there are no error messages, this means that you have selected the correct backup file.</string>
    <string name="RestoreStep3">Wait a few seconds for your notes to be restored. Once the restore process is complete, verify that your notes have been restored correctly.</string>
    <string name="RestoreStep4">If you have not already deleted the backup file, make sure to delete it once you are done with the restore process. This will help prevent any potential security issues or data loss.</string>
    <string name="BackupInfo">SaveNote includes a useful feature called "Backup," which allows you to create a copy of all your notes and save them to a file. This file can be used to transfer your notes to another device or to restore them to your current device if you ever experience data loss or device failure.</string>
    <string name="InstructionsOrder">%s. </string>
</resources>